Close

* Pro space

Privacy Policy
==============

Introduction
------------

With the development of new tools of communication, it is important to pay attention to private data protection. Which is why we are committed to respecting the privacy of the personal information we collect on our different our brain training applications: COCO THINKS and COCO MOVES, COCO PENSE e COCO SI MUOVE, Scarlett, Clint, Edith, Joe, Roberto, Sofia, Annelies, Carmen, Fernando, Zhiqu and Iqu, The Rolling Ball, Top Culture / Top Kids developed by DYNSEO.

Information Collection and Use
------------------------------

Personal information about an individual may include the following:

* Last name
* First name
* Email
* Gender / Sex
* Age / Date of birth

We may collect information through forms and thanks to the interactivity existing between you and our website. We also use, as mentioned hereafter, cookies and/or surveys to collect information about you.

Forms and interactive features:
-------------------------------

Your personal information is collected through the use of forms, such as:

* Registration to the website,
* Registration within the apps.

We use the collected information for the following purposes:

* Contact information
* Performance statistics

The DYNSEO brand is a registered trademark.

The DYNSEO apps have processed by the CNIL, who conducted June 11, 2013 under the number 1679021.

The websites [www.dynseo.com](http://www.dynseo.com/) et [www.stimart.com](http://www.stimart.com/) are hosted by OVH, located at 2 rue Kellermann – 59100 Roubaix – France.

Right of objection and erasure
------------------------------

We are committed to providing you with a right of objection and erasure regarding your personal information.

The right to object is understood ad being the possibility offered to the Internet users to refuse that their personal information be used for certain purposes mentioned at the time of collection.

The right to erasure is understood as being the possibility offered to Internet user to ask that their personal information no longer appear, for example, in a mailing list.

To exercise these rights, you can contact us by email at the following addresses:

* by mail at this address: 6 rue du Docteur Finlay, 75015 Paris,
* by email at [justine.sauquet@dynseo.com](mailto:justine.sauquet@dynseo.com) by phone at this number: +33966938422.

Website section: [https://www.stimart.com/](https://www.stimart.com/)

Right of access
---------------

We grant you the right of access and rectification to your personal data, if you wish to consult, modify or even delete information.

The exercise of this right will be made by mail to the address:

* by mail at this address: 6 rue du Docteur Finlay, 75015 Paris,
* by email at: [justine.sauquet@dynseo.com,](mailto:justine.sauquet@dynseo.com)
* Phone: +33666240826

Website section: [https://www.stimart.com/](https://www.stimart.com/)

Security of datas
-----------------

Personal data that we collect, is stored in a secured environment. People working for us are required to respect the confidentiality of personal data. To ensure its security, we use the following measures:

* SSL protocol (Secure Sockets Layer)
* Access management – Authorized person
* Access management – person concerned
* Computer backup
* Log in/ Password

We are committed to maintaining a high level of confidentiality by incorporating the latest technological innovations to ensure confidentiality of your data. However, since no mechanism provides maximum security, some risk is always present when using the Internet to transmit personal information. 

For the COCO THINKS and COCO MOVES app, we undertake to comply with the rules for Play family content.

Legislation
-----------

We undertake to respect the legislative provisions set out in Law 78-17 “INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY, DATA FILES AND CIVIL LIBERTIES.”

All Internet user dispose of the right of objection (Article 38 of the above-mentioned law), the right of access (Article 39, 41 and 42 of the above-mentioned law) and of rectification (Article 40 of the above-mentioned law) regarding their personal data.

DYNSEO 2013 - 2022
